I got an Alexa in my house everybody's
spying on
me that's it I just got an Alexa in the
house so things are really starting to
come together you know if you don't know
what it is it's like a little speaker
you put in your house you talk to it it
Google stuff for you it plays music it
listens to everything you say it sends
it to the government it's
in after we got this the first time my
wife asked she's like do you think it
does that do you think it spies on us
and sends it to the government I was
like yeah
probably we just put a microphone hooked
to the internet on our coffee table
I hope it's only the
government I hope it's not some dude
named Hank who's good with computers and
likes the sound of our
voices that would be way worse doe the
German one again I like that that's not
what you
want on the other
side I used to get paranoid about that
stuff but you can't anymore they're
putting all the technology everywhere
they came out with an Alexa powered
microwave yeah they put Alexa in a
microwave so now you can use your voice
to control your
microwave while you're standing directly
in
front of your
microwave you still have to get up and
put the food in there nobody's doing
that for you like do we need that when
they figured out instead of pressing two
0 0 you could just press the two for 2
minutes that's when microwave technology
peaked we need to go any further than
that now instead of going Boop you have
to go
Alexa Alexa
Alexa set the microwave for 2 minutes
setting the microwave for 20 minutes no
stop I'm very disrespectful to her in
the
house it's going to come back to bite me
when they take over but for now it feels
really
good I don't like it as much as I
thought I was going to I thought I was
going to feel like living with a robot
like live with an AI I'm in the future I
got little robot buddy in the house but
it's the voice I think she sounds too
real it just feels like I'm living with
a person that's better at Googling stuff
than I am like I wish Microsoft would
come out with an Alexa that's powered by
Microsoft Sam and he's just upset
everyone had forgotten about him all
these years like hey Sam
what what's what's the weather like out
today why don't you look out the window
yourselves you lazy human
kills that's what I
want I just want a little thing playing
pranks on me all day hey Sam set a timer
for 5es setting self-destruct timer for
seconds LOL that would be
fun put Sam in the microwave have no
problem with your diet hey Sam start up
that microwave an entire bag of buttered
popcorn is not a snack okay I wasn't
going to eat all it
anyway I love how some of you laughed at
that voice some of you just stared
straight through me like he has the
devil inside of
him we should leave immediately
it freaks my dog out too she hates it
come on let's go for a walk I'm not
going anywhere with you you smell
different I hate
that it comes in handy though that's the
voice I use on the phone anytime I got
one of those scammers calling me about
my vehicle warranty or something they
don't know what to do
hello and thank you for
calling please wait for the next
available
representative Primos your estimated we
time is is is is is is they hang up on
me now it's pretty sweet I don't know
what to do